tackledirect.com 2019-08-18

# TackleDirect Privacy & Security

**CONFIDENTIALITY**

TackleDirect has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for TackleDirect.

TackleDirect is committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection and management of personal information you share with us (the phrase "personal information" means any information by which you can be identified, such as your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, etc.). The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you what personal information we may collect from you, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review and correct, the information. This policy applies only to customers in the United States.

As a part of our commitment to your privacy, TackleDirect supports and adheres to the guidelines and practices adopted by the Direct Marketing Association's "Privacy Promise to American Consumers." We have agreed to (1) provide customers with notice of their ability to opt out of information rental, sale or exchange with other marketers; (2) honor customers' requests not to share their information with other marketers; and (3) honor customers' requests not to receive mail, telephone or other solicitations from TackleDirect.

 **Collecting Information About You**

There may be times (such as when you purchase or order a product, subscribe to a service, register to receive catalogs, or to participate in contests, sweepstakes or promotions, etc.) when we ask you to provide certain information about yourself, such as your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, birth date, gender, occupation, personal interests, etc. We may also maintain a record of your product purchases.

Whether or not to provide such information is completely your own choice. But if you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to purchase products, or access certain services, offers and content on our web site. In addition, we may need to contact you via phone, email or mail to address questions or issues specific to your order, entry, etc., even if you have opted to not receive communications from us.

In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We may track the Internet domain address from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but individual users will remain anonymous, unless you voluntarily tell us who you are.

TackleDirect may collect your email address via cookies and pixels on the website through the use of trusted third party partners. These partners may combine your email information with other information they have access to such as a mailing address so that TackleDirect may serve relevant marketing offers to you via direct mail. If you do not want TackleDirect to collect information about you, please contact us to opt out via email, live chat, or by phone.

 **Using Information About You**

We use the personal information you provide for internal purposes, such as confirming and tracking your order, subscription or registration, analyzing trends and statistics, informing you of our new products, services and offers, and providing you with information from and about TackleDirect. From time to time we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy policies are consistent with ours. These are known as our TackleDirect Partners. In such cases we might share and cross-reference information, including personal information about you that will enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you.

To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online, in our stores or through our catalogs. We may also combine that information with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with our TackleDirect Partners and others. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.

We may contract with companies or persons to provide certain services including credit card processing, shipping, data management, promotional services, etc. We call them our Service Providers. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. We also ask our Service Providers to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours.

Although unlikely, in certain instances we may disclose your personal information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to TackleDirect or to others. We may also disclose your personal information when we believe the law requires it.

 **Editing, Updating, Correcting and Deleting Information About You**

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive information from TackleDirect or from the TackleDirect Partners please let us know by calling us at 1-888-354-7335, by sending us an [email](mailto:sales@tackledirect.com).. Please be sure to include your email address, mailing address, full name, and specifically what information you do not want to receive. If you would like to update or correct your email address, mailing address or other personal information with us please contact us the same way.

Please note that any requests to remove or update your personal information may take up to ten days for your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request.

 **Protecting Children**

TackleDirect takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of children. Our web sites are general audience sites. We do not permit anyone under the age of 13 to register with us. We also do not send email correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13 without their parent's consent.

Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any personal information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children's online activities and use parental control or other web filtering technology to supervise children's access to the web.

 **Cookies**

Our web sites use "cookies." A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our products and services to suit your personal interests, estimate our audience size, assist our online merchants to track visits to and sales at our sites and to process your order, track your status in our promotions, contests and sweepstakes, and/or analyze your visiting patterns. You can generally set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

We may contract with third parties who may use cookies and collect information on our behalf. These third parties are prohibited by our contract with them from sharing that information with anyone other than us or our Service Providers. However, we respect your right to choose whether to be included in such services. If you would like to opt out of these services, please contact us.

 **Security**

We take precautions, including use of sophisticated encryption and authentication tools, to protect the security of your personal information that you share with us. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our web sites, and you do so at your own risk.

We urge you to keep your password in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also remember to log off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place such as a library or Internet cafe.

 **Links to Third Party Sites**

Our web sites may contain links to web sites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked sites may be different from our privacy policy. You access such linked sites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked site before disclosing any personal information on such site.

This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the [Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information.

 **Policy Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our web site. Those changes will go into effect on the date posted in the notice. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our web site and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. This policy was posted in December 2006.

 **Your Feedback**

To help us improve our privacy policy and practice, please give us your feedback. You may contact us at the information below. 

**1\. SECURITY ASSURANCE**  
TackleDirect guarantee's that your credit card information is safe with us! In an effort to further protect the consumer against fraudulent charges, TackleDirect offers our customers total security assurance.

1) First, our site uses the latest in encryption technology, digital certificates, secure commerce servers and authentication to ensure that your personal information is secure online. TackleDirect uses digital certificates from Verisign, Inc., a trusted third-party Certification Authority (CA). Also known as Digital IDs, these digital certificates are similar to your driver's license, passport or membership card in that they prove your identity. Digital IDs are useful in electronic commerce because they verify the identity of the parties involved. Making a credit card purchase at TackleDirect is actually more secure than using your credit card at the local store or restaurant. 

2) TackleDirect uses 128 bit encryption for maximum security for communications over the Internet. Furthermore, TackleDirect ensures the privacy of the information not only online, but through our back-end systems. 

According to CNN, "The prevalent opinion...is that on-line credit card use is actually no riskier for consumers than traditional "low-tech" transactions." We order products online all the time, both as a company and as individuals. When we use a credit card to buy something online, we feel at least as safe as we would using one in a store or restaurant.

**2\. CHOICE / OPT-OUT**  
TackleDirect provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.

We gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

**3\. CORRECT / UPDATE**  
To correct or update any information send us an email: [sales@tackledirect.com](mailto:sales@tackledirect.com)

**4\. HOW TO CONTACT US**

**Phone:**  
Toll-Free: 1-888-35-4REEL  
Direct: 1-609-788-3819  
Hours: Weekdays - 8am to 6pm ET  
Weekends - 9am to 6pm ET   

**Mail:**  
TackleDirect Sales Dept.  
6825 Tilton Road, Bldg C  
Egg Harbor Twp, NJ 08234-4426  
USA
